maxiaids.com 2019-07-04

# MaxiAids | Privacy & Security

**Security**

Latest Internet Technology provides us with the safest way of doing business with your credit card. MaxiAids.com has made it safer to use your credit card and personal information on our Web site than to use it in more traditional ways.

MaxiAids.com uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology for mutual authentication, data encryption and data integrity all of which allows ensuring secure transactions. SSL is the industry standard security protocol to encode sensitive information, such as your personal information and credit card number. SSL creates a shared digital key, which only lets the sender and the receiver of the transmission scramble or unscramble information. Most keys range from 40 to 1,024 digits long producing the number of possible combinations into the billions and beyond!

MaxiAids.com collects your information via SSL secure connection providing you with the safest shopping experience. After you submit your information it is placed in encrypted form on our secure server. When we retrieve your order from our secure server it also done over secure connection in order to provide you with **100% secure online ordering**.

**Privacy Statement**

**MaxiAids.com is committed to protecting your privacy. MaxiAids.com does not sell, trade, exchange, or rent your personal information to a third party**. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide you with additional information that you can find useful. MaxiAids.com will not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information. The following is on collection of the information from you and its use:

When you order, we request your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, and credit card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. When you enter a contest, sweepstake, or other promotional feature, we may ask you for your name, address, and email address or any additional information in order to enter you in a promotional feature. Additionally we use collected information to administer the promotional feature and notify winners.

We may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes at MaxiAids.com and special offers you will find useful. If you would rather not receive this information, send us request to be removed from the list. We may collect certain technical information, which does not allow us to identify you personally, but pertains to your use of the Internet. For example, on the Web such information may include the type of Internet Browser or Monitor Resolution you are using. This information enables us to enhance our Web site’ content and compatibility with your computer system.

By using MaxiAids.com Web site you consent to the collection and use of this information by MaxiAids.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes in our Privacy Statement so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

If you are under 18 years of age, you must have your parent or guardian’s permission to order products or services. MaxiAids.com uses a feature of your Internet Web browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. MaxiAids.com only uses cookies to keep track of items you put into your shopping cart and your ordering information, and to help us determine whether you came to MaxiAids.com from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement. Cookies cannot be used by MaxiAids.com to retrieve any personal information about you. MaxiAids.com does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by you.

**Personal and Credit Card Information Security**

Whenever you enter sensitive personal information such as credit card numbers or login to your account with password on our website, our website encrypts the information you send to, and receive from, the site. When you log into your MaxiAids account or go through purchasing process, you will always be on a secure website.

You can see that our website is using SSL security in two ways:

Additionally, when you double click lock icon at the bottom left or bottom right of your browser window, Certificate information will be displayed confirming authenticity of the secure certificate. 

**Shopping at MaxiAids.com is always 100% safe and secure!**
